{
    "subject": "resource/Compelled",
    "predicate": "property/starring",
    "object": "resource/Ronald_Howard_(British_actor)",
    "human_readable": "Compelled is starring Ronald Howard (British actor).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7802227139472961,
            "question": "Are there any other actors in Compelled besides Ronald Howard?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7760122418403625,
            "question": "Who is starring in the movie Compelled?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7384013533592224,
            "question": "Has Ronald Howard won any awards for his role in Compelled?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6024287939071655,
            "question": "Is Ronald Howard known for any other roles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45977532863616943,
            "question": "What nationality is Ronald Howard?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40211254358291626,
            "question": "What is the director of the movie Compelled?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3320314288139343,
            "question": "When was the movie Compelled released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27594661712646484,
            "question": "What genre is the movie Compelled likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2323664128780365,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the plot of Compelled?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17148081958293915,
            "question": "Where can I watch Compelled?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Compelled is starring Ronald Howard (British actor).",
            "html": "dbpedia_3058_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the plot of Compelled?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3058_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the movie Compelled likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3058_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was the movie Compelled released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3058_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3058_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3058_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3058_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3058_139.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3058_163.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3058_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3058_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3058_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3058_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3058_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have more triples you'd like me to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that Ronald Howard was a British actor and provide details about his filmography, including his role in the film \"Compelled Reviews,\" which aligns with the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}